Andrew LaBorde

Golden, CO 80401

(214) 477-5926 | andrew.lab14@gmail.com

GitHub: https://github.com/AndyLaBorde | LinkedIn: https://github.com/AndyLaBorde | LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/andrew-laborde-dev/ | Portfolio: https://andylaborde.github.io/Portfolio-React/

Summary

Full-Stack Web Developer leveraging a background of management in the service industry with a desire for continuous learning, problem-solving and collaboration. Experienced in managing customer relations by bridging the gap between the owners expectations and the productivity of the team. Strong ability to design, maintain and build web applications from conception to production.

Technical Skills

Software Development, Software Deployment, C/C++, Python, Ruby on Rails, Linux, SQL, Sequelize, Git, GitHub, Git Bash, PostgreSQL, Flask, Django, MySQL, JavaScript, jQuery, User Interface (UI), REST, Node.js, Test cases/jest, Heroku, Express.js, HTML5, Bootstrap, CSS, NoSQL, MongoDB, AGILE methodologies, Scrum, Kanban, Wire-Framing, Database Diagrams

Projects

https://frogr-app.herokuapp.com/
https://book-search-app.herokuapp.com/
https://pawsome.herokuapp.com/
https://andylaborde.github.io/G-Query/

Experience

Jamba Auntie Anne's, Wylie, TX — General Manager

June 2021 - August 2022

- Implementing financial tools and analyzing financial reports to identify and address trends and issues in store performance
- Manage Profit and Loss, store-level sales and financial such as staffing and inventory costs
- Training, coaching, counseling and disciplining team members and shift managers
- Embody transparent leadership style with emphasis on team engagement and accountability

Buffalo Bill's Good Eats, Rowlette, TX — Head Cook, Kitchen Manager

December 2020 - June 2021

- New training manuals and employee handbooks created and implemented on all levels
- Product ordering and waste management
- Directing a team of 5 cooks during peaks and lulls for optimal efficiency with minimum waste
- Training, coaching, counseling and disciplining team members and shift managers

Emerald City Management, Dallas, TX — Lighting Director

January 2019 - April 2020

- Program unique performances for each event
- Direct pre-event meetings for all crew to ensure a smooth production

- Direct lighting crew and stage set up
- Maintenance lighting equipment

Education

University of Denver, Denver, CO October 2022 - Present

Full Stack Web Development Certificate

Texas A&M, College Station, TX August 2021 - August 2022

Mechanical Engineering - Undergraduate

Dallas College, Dallas, TX January 2019 - May 2022

Associate of Science - Engineering

Coding Dojo, Dallas, TX October 2017 - February 2018

Full Stack Web Development Certificate